

JOHN KERWIN OROPEZA

Full Stack Developer/Software Deployment

About Me

I am a proficient web developer and software deployment specialist who is dedicated to creating exceptional experiences and ensuring their successful deployment. My expertise in web development and deployment strategies makes me a valuable asset to any team or project, and I look forward to contributing my skills to drive success in your endeavors.



09678991909



johnkerwinoropeza3@gmail.com



Sitio Langub, Kalunasan Cebu City

LANGUAGES / FRAMEWORKS

- HTML
- Tailwind CSS
- CSS
- Git
- Bootstrap
- Linux Ubuntu
- JavaScript
- Docker
- · React js
- MySQL
- Next js
- Hyper V
- PHP
- CentOS
- Laravel
- MongoDB
- MXAMPP.
- JAVA
- JSON
- WAN LAN

EXPERIENCE

Rameses Systems Inc Software Deployment team Mabolo, Cebu City March 2023 - October 2023

Installation of software, upgrading, maintenance, technical client support.

Maintain, migration of database, and back up management.

KodeGo Full Stack Development Trainee Manila Philippines

June 2022 - November 2022

Created websites that are user-friendly, mobile responsive.

Demonstrated various front-end and back-end languages and frameworks.

Bakery Equipment Technician Sinmag Bakery Machine Corp Manila Philippines 2010- 2018

Commissioning, and installation of bakery equipment. Troubleshoot and repair.

EDUCATION

University of San Jose - Recoletos

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering 2002 (3rd year college)

Abellana National School

High School 1999

https://github.com/johnkerwin123 https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-kerwin-oropeza-2b2817240/